<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv>
  <channel id="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10">
    <display-name>ZEE CLASSIC RS-0.10</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20250212005600 +0530" stop="20250212025700 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Faisla</title>
    <desc>Three cruel and heartless convicts escape from prison to avenge the rape and death of one of their daughters. However, a turn of events leads them to committing other heinous crimes.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212025700 +0530" stop="20250212053800 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>April Fool</title>
    <desc>Ashok, a prankster, loves pulling off practical jokes. Each April Fool`s day, he simply outdoes himself. But one such joke gets him and Madhu in so much trouble that they have to run for their lives.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212053800 +0530" stop="20250212070100 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Dastaan-E-Rafi</title>
    <desc>Dastaan-E-Rafi explores the life of legendary singer Mohd. Rafi through memories.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212070100 +0530" stop="20250212094800 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Yari Dushmani</title>
    <desc>Shankar and Birju, orphaned friends, face betrayal and greed after looting a wedding. As Shankar seeks revenge and diamonds, tension rises with dacoits and their complicated past.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212094800 +0530" stop="20250212122500 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Razia Sultan</title>
    <desc>Razia Sultan, the first female ruler of the Delhi Sultanate, lands in trouble and loses her kingdom when she falls in love with Jamal-ud-Din Yakut, an Abyssinian slave.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212122500 +0530" stop="20250212161100 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Tamacha</title>
    <desc>After years, when childhood best friends Raju and Vicky unite, they have a showdown as one becomes a cop and the other is a notorious criminal, who find themselves on the opposite sides of the law.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212161100 +0530" stop="20250212190000 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Allah Rakha</title>
    <desc>Street urchin Allah Rakha discovers that his parents are alive and that the family was separated by a mafia don. He sets out for revenge.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212190000 +0530" stop="20250212215800 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Kasam Suhaag Ki</title>
    <desc>A wounded serpent seeks revenge on the killers of her husband. Does she finally manage to succeed in her mission?</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250212215800 +0530" stop="20250213004800 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Kalicharan</title>
    <desc>Kalicharan a criminal serving a life sentence is given bail to take place of late Inspector as he resembles him.</desc>
    <date>20250212</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213004800 +0530" stop="20250213025500 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Sabak</title>
    <desc>A story of a police Sub-Inspector. It tells of how he goes about single-handed to smash a notorious smugglers gang to avenge the murder of his Brother.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213025500 +0530" stop="20250213052300 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Jhanak Jhanak Payal Baaje</title>
    <desc>Dance maestro Mangal pairs Neela with his son, Girdhar, for a competition. As their romance blossoms, they become distracted, jeopardizing their performance and Mangal`s hopes for their success.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213052300 +0530" stop="20250213092900 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Shree 420</title>
    <desc>Raj is a naive man who comes to Mumbai to fulfil his dreams. However, he gets influenced by a conniving man who promises the world to him.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213092900 +0530" stop="20250213125100 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Dhan Daulat</title>
    <desc>A man is forced to end a relationship, unaware that his lover is pregnant. Later, father and son meet but will they discover each other`s identities?</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213125100 +0530" stop="20250213160900 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Sanjog</title>
    <desc>Asha`s life turns upside down when she realizes that her guardians are not her real parents and her real mother is mentally ill.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213160900 +0530" stop="20250213190000 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Ganga Tere Desh Mein</title>
    <desc>Inspector Ajay arrests a mentally disturbed gangster. Intrigued by his own mother`s kindness towards the culprit, Ajay decides to find out the truth, which may change his outlook towards life.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213190000 +0530" stop="20250213221500 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Main Tulsi Tere Aangan Ki</title>
    <desc>The story of a woman who switched roles from being a prostitute to being a most loving mother to a child who is not even her own.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250213221500 +0530" stop="20250214012900 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Karz</title>
    <desc>Monty uncovers the truth about his past life, discovering he was killed by his gold-digger wife while his family was left homeless. With his lover`s support, he seeks justice.</desc>
    <date>20250213</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214012900 +0530" stop="20250214034800 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Do Phool</title>
    <desc>A wealthy man disowns his two irresponsible sons. One of them plays a prank by claiming that he has murdered his brother.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214034800 +0530" stop="20250214064200 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Saaransh</title>
    <desc>A retired school teacher and his wife come to terms with life after the death of their only son in a senseless mugging incident.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214064200 +0530" stop="20250214095500 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Aakhri Dao</title>
    <desc>Ravi, a reformed burglar, builds a new life but is tempted back into crime when an old partner offers him a dangerous job, threatening his redemption.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214095500 +0530" stop="20250214125600 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Woh 7 Din</title>
    <desc>Dr Anand learns that his new bride loves someone else. He decides to re-unite the two lovers at all costs and begins to search for the man.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214125600 +0530" stop="20250214162200 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Alag Alag</title>
    <desc>A village belle marries an older doctor for his money, while singer Neeraj moves in with a movie starlet in the hope of getting more work. However, unexpected events occur and change their lives.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214162200 +0530" stop="20250214190000 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Qayamat</title>
    <desc>Two close friends turn into foes when they grow up, as one turns into a criminal and the other, an IPS Officer.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214190000 +0530" stop="20250214222000 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Satyam Shivam Sundaram</title>
    <desc>Rajeev falls for Roopa, a beautiful singer concealing half her disfigured face. After marriage, he discovers her secret and starts to ignore her, leading to emotional turmoil in their relationship.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250214222000 +0530" stop="20250215011200 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Bombay To Goa</title>
    <desc>Mala, a young girl, witnesses a murder and boards a bus bound for Goa to escape from the killer. As a result, she meets exciting people from different cultures who make her journey adventurous.</desc>
    <date>20250214</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215011200 +0530" stop="20250215033500 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Aap To Aise Na The</title>
    <desc>A man loses the love of his life to the best friend he owes all his success to. Can he win her back or did she not love him at all?</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215033500 +0530" stop="20250215070300 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Dada</title>
    <desc>When a young, simple boy witnesses a shoot-out of a don and manages to save his life, the don trains him to be his successor.</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215070300 +0530" stop="20250215093800 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Itihaas (1987)</title>
    <desc>Joginder, an honest police commissioner, is instrumental in arresting Alexander, a dreaded gangster. Alexander is granted bail by the court and as revenge he molests Joginder`s daughter Jyoti.</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215093800 +0530" stop="20250215131300 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Kudrat</title>
    <desc>Choudry Janak Singh, a man she hasn`t met before, is the face in Chandramukhi`s nightmares. Can Naresh,a psychiatrist, help her?</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215131300 +0530" stop="20250215162300 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Mere Jeevan Saathi</title>
    <desc>An artist loses his eyesight in a tragic accident and is helped by a stranger. He later discovers the woman he loves is set to marry the same man who helped him.</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215162300 +0530" stop="20250215190000 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Hafta Vasuli</title>
    <desc>Lotiram Khabadia, a corrupt MLA, teams up with gangster Tamancha to win elections but faces defeat from Chayavati. Betrayed, he plans revenge, risking everything to testify.</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215190000 +0530" stop="20250215215300 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Andheri Raat Mein Diya Tere Haath Mein</title>
    <desc>Two friends dive into the underworld for riches and luxury. But when one sees the dark side of their choices, he yearns for a more normal, fulfilling life.</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20250215215300 +0530" stop="20250216012900 +0530" channel="ZEE_CLASSIC_RS-0.10" clumpidx="0/1">
    <title>Batwara</title>
    <desc>Amidst the fall of princely states in post-independence India, the friendship between aristocrat Vikram and a peasant is tested. Vikram turns vengeful after his brother is killed in a peasant colony.</desc>
    <date>20250215</date>
  </programme>
</tv>